He's not a bodyguard
He's the long-lost heir of the Fu Group
When was the Fu Group's announcement made
10 minutes ago
How are the partners reacting
Uh
Speak
The Lu Group requested a reassessment
of the West City Yunwan project risk
And they hope the upcoming risk control meetings
will include Mr. Fu Chenzhou
Banks also asked if Gu Group's earlier
judgments and views on Mr. Fu's identity
had significant errors
This isn't sarcasm
It's a business judgment error
Chengze
Is the Fu Group's announcement true
I'm just worried about you
Are you worried about me
or yourself
Because you pretended to be an old acquaintance
The Fu Group's impression of the Gu family
will only get worse now
Where are you going Mr Gu
The Fu Group
Are you going to look for Fu Chenzhou
The one who should regret isn't me
Su Mingyao
When exactly did you find out